# Deinyefa Eporwei

# Virtual Reality and Games Developer | df.eporwei@gmail.com

# **Summary**

With a background in Earth Science and a creative curiosity about uses of new technology, I develop immersive gaming experiences.

My passion lies within the amazing technology of virtual reality, and its ability to transform the world for the better. I have spent the past year building applications and games for Oculus Rift, HTC Vive, Gear VR, and Google Cardboard.

I learn by developing and contributing to open source VR and cross-platform games, including Puzzler, Tetro, and MazeVR. In my spare time, I write about my developer experience and find ways to assist other developers on their software journey.

## **Education**

## **B.S.C | JULY 2017 | CARLETON UNIVERSITY**

· Major: Earth Sciences

# VR NANODEGREE | 2017 | UDACITY

· Major: Modelling, Virtual Environments and Simulation

# **Skills & Expertise**

- · Unity3D
- · Game Development
- · Virtual Reality
- · Team Building
- · Research
- · Web Development

# **Projects**

#### **MAZEVR**

- · November 2016 to December 2016
- This VR game challenges the user to try to go through the maze and into the temple to collect the hidden treasure and win the game.

#### **PUZZLER**

- · December 2016 to January 2017
- The puzzler is a mobile VR game targeted towards new VR users that challenge them to solve a simple puzzle in a new way. The player is presented with a pattern and is charged with replicating that model to beat the game.

#### **TETRO**

- · July 2016 to August 2016
- Tetro is a simple 2D remake of the classic Tetris game.

# **Experience**

## VIRTUAL REALITY / UNITY DEVELOPER | MARCH 2016 - PRESENT

• Explore, prototype, and develop projects with a focus on immersive experiences using and mixing technologies such as virtual reality, mixed reality, and motion tracking.

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER | LIVELOVE.CA | MAY 2016 - PRESENT

- Work with a team of Web designers and developers to update and maintain the public website of <a href="http://livelove.ca">http://livelove.ca</a>.
- · Technologies used:
  - · HTML
  - · CSS
  - · PHP (Laravel Framework)
  - · JQuery

## ACCOUNTANT | LIVING SPRING | DECEMBER 2013 - MAY 2016

- · Preparing and entering contributions to specific fund accounts such as general fund, building funds, and charity fund
- · Handling bookkeeping activities and maintaining confidentiality of information